Hello everyone, there are job openings in ICI Lombard Company
and it is
completely working jobs. If
you see here, they have released a total of 50
posts. The
job roll of this job is Tilly Sales
Executive.
Anyone who has completed graduation can attend
this interview. And if you see its
experience, both freshers
and anyone with below five years of experience can
apply. The
job location is Navi Mumbai
and it is completely in office full time
job. If you see here,
its total salary package is 175
to 2.5 lakhs per month. And if you
see its interview date, you can attend the
job interview anytime between November 11 and November 16.
The timing
is  10:30 am to 4:30 pm If you
want the full details of this, we will
mention its link in the description,
you can check it out from there.